

- 622-101-08-14
- vivian.munguia.mtz@gmail.
- www.linkedin.com/in/ vivianmunguia/

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Communication
- · Problem-Solving
- Fast Learner
- Committed
- Responsible

LANGUAGES

- Spanish 100%
- English 85%

ABILITIES

- C#
- Xamarin
- SQL
- Git

VIVIAN MUNGUÍA

PROGRAMMER

PROFILE

I am a professional with a bachelor's degree in Software Engineering, My experience is in desktop application development with C#, as well as in mobile application development with Xamarin. I am a hard worker oriented to results and I am always challenging myself to continuously improve.

WORK EXPERIENCE

St. Clair Technologies | Programmer Analyst

January 2022 - April 2023

- Desktop application development and maintenance.
- Mobile application development and maintenance.
- Reduced scanning cycle time from 10 minutes per cycle to real time scanning.
- Mobile application development to transfer material from one plant to another.

St. Clair Technologies | IT Technician

March 2021 - January 2022

- Desktop application maintenance.
- · Report creation with crystal reports.
- Mobile application maintenance.
- Desktop application development to manage projects.

EDUCATION

Instituto Tecnológico de Sonora, Campus Guaymas 2015-2019

Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering - Title